(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
In a kingdom far far away
where all nyut-nyut lives,
A sudden calamity strikes
among the nyut-nyut who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has emerged out of nowhere
and created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left hopeless
until a mysterious magical squirrel arrived
to find a legendary weapon, the Nut Blade.
The legend said that this mysterious squirrel
will bring an end to this calamity...
強くなれる
I learned the reason...
理由を知った
...to be strong.
僕を連れて
Take me with you...
進め
...and move forward.
紅蓮華
Lyrics: LiSA Music: 草野華余子
Gurenge
Lyrics: LiSA Music: Kayoko Kusano
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
I get drunk on the muddy revolving lantern.
こわばる心 震える手は
My stiff heart and trembling hands
掴みたいものがある
Have something they want to seize.
それだけさ
That is all.
夜の匂いに
In the scent of the night,
空睨んでも
Even if I glare at the sky,
変わっていけるのは自分自身だけ
The only one who can change things is myself.
それだけさ
That is all.
強くなれる理由を知った
I learned the reason to be strong.
僕を連れて進め
Take me with you and move forward!
どうしたって！ 消せない夢も
No matter what! Dreams that cannot be erased,
止まれない今も
And the present that cannot be stopped,
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else,
ありがとう
Thank you,
悲しみよ
Sadness!
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
I learned the meaning of defeat, beaten down by the world.
紅蓮の華よ 咲き誇れ
Oh crimson lotus flower, bloom proudly!
運命を照らして
Illuminate my destiny.
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning pierces my ears.
戸惑う心 優しいだけじゃ
A bewildered heart; with kindness alone,
守れないものがある
There are things I cannot protect.
わかってるけど
I understand that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪
Good and evil entangled beneath the surface,
透けて見える偽善に天罰
Divine punishment for the visible hypocrisy.
(Tell me why, Tell me why, Tell me why, Tell me why)
I don't need you!
逸材の花より
Rather than a talented flower,
挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
A single flower that kept challenging and bloomed is beautiful.
乱暴に敷き詰められた
On this roughly paved,
トゲだらけの道も
Thorn-covered path,
本気の僕だけに現れるから
It appears only because I am serious.
乗り越えて
I will overcome it,
みせるよ
I'll show you.
簡単に片付けられた守れなかった夢も
Dreams that were easily dismissed and unprotected,
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
Take root in this crimson heart,
この血に
And in this blood,
宿って
Dwell.
人知れず儚い 散りゆく結末
A fleeting, scattering ending unknown to anyone.
無情に破れた 悲鳴の風吹く
Ruthlessly torn, the wind of screams blows.
誰かの笑う影
Someone's laughing shadow,
誰かの泣き声
Someone's crying voice,
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness.
どうしたって！ 消せない夢も
No matter what! Dreams that cannot be erased,
止まれない今も
And the present that cannot be stopped,
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else,
ありがとう
Thank you,
悲しみよ
Sadness!
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
I learned the meaning of defeat, beaten down by the world.
紅蓮の華よ 咲き誇れ
Oh crimson lotus flower, bloom proudly!
運命を照らして
Illuminate my destiny.
運命を
My destiny...
照らして
...Illuminate it.
Oh no...
Everything is burned down.
My house and the entire village is destroyed.
What is going on?
Are you alright?
A giant monster...
Burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad.
Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry.
I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that,
I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager.
Oh, I will.
星を廻せ
Spin the stars
世界の真ん中で
In the center of the world
くしゃみすれば
If I sneeze
どこかの森で蝶が乱舞
Butterflies dance wildly in some forest
君が守る
You guard
ドアの鍵デタラメ
The door key is nonsense
恥ずかしい物語
An embarrassing story
舐め合っても
Even if we lick each other's wounds
ライオンは強い
The lion is strong
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
I start wanting to live more
星座の導きで今
Guided by the constellations, now
見つめ合った
We stared at each other
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方に暮れて
Lost in bewilderment
キラリ枯れてゆく
Sparkling as I wither away
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body
私眠らない
I won't sleep
風はやがて
The wind will soon
東へ向かうだろう
Head towards the east
高気圧
High pressure
この星の氷河を襲う
Attacks the glaciers of this planet
誘い水を
The pump priming water
飲んだ胸が痛い
My chest hurts from drinking it
遠巻きな物語
A story from a distance
かじり合う
Gnawing at each other
骨の奥まで
Deep into the bone
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きてたくなる
I start wanting to live more
星座の導きで今
Guided by the constellations, now
見つめ合った
We stared at each other
生き残りたい
I want to survive
途方に暮れて
Lost in bewilderment
キラリ枯れてゆく
Sparkling as I wither away
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body
私眠らない
I won't sleep
We shouted to survive
Woah-oh-oh
何しに生まれたの
Why was I born?
何しにここにいる
Why am I here?
生き残りたい
I want to survive
埋まらない傷
Unfilled wounds
光恐れてた
I feared the light
許された命が今
The forgiven life, now
引かれ合った
Was drawn together
さまよい果てて
Wandering to the end
君の隣で
Beside you
火照り鎮めたい
I want to calm this heat
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true body
私眠らない
I won't sleep
生き残りたい
I want to survive
崖っぷちでいい
The edge of the cliff is fine
君を愛してる
I love you
目覚めたい本能が今
The instinct to awaken, now
引かれ合った
Was drawn together
正気に戻って
Return to sanity
祈り捧ぐよ
And offer a prayer
君を愛してる
I love you
星座の導きで...
Guided by the constellations...
生き残りたい
I want to survive
まだ生きてたい
I still want to live
君を愛してる
I love you
本気の心見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true heart
私眠らない
I won't sleep
星が降る
Stars fall...
羽もない
I, who have no wings,
この私が
this very self,
憧れてた
yearned for
あの空
that sky.
背伸びして
Standing on tiptoes,
星をつかむ
to grab a star,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate it.
負けないで
Don't lose,
願いさえも
even to the wishes
飲み込む闇
that the darkness swallows.
それでも
Even so,
手探りで
groping blindly,
夢のかけら
fragments of a dream...
集めにいこうよ
let's go collect them.
ただぐるぐる回る
Just spinning round and round
車輪の中で
inside the wheel.
走っても
Run and run...
run and run...
たどり着けなくて
unable to reach the end.
先を行く君の
I was only watching the back
背中ばかりを見ていた
of you who went ahead.
いつか越えられる
Someday I can surpass you,
もっと強くなりたい
I want to become stronger.
たったひとり
Born all alone,
生まれてきた
into this world,
その記憶も
losing even that memory,
なくして
I lost it.
泣き声も
Even if I lament
届かないと
that my cries don't reach...
嘆いてみても
try as I might to grieve,
信じていい
is it okay to believe?
大きな木にしがみついた
Clung to a big tree...
爪痕
these claw marks.
あの空へ
To that sky,
近づこうと
trying to get closer...
している証
this is the proof.
風が雲を流して
The wind blows the clouds away.
あぁ
Ah...
星が降る
Stars fall.
羽もない
I, who have no wings,
この私が
this very self,
憧れてた
yearned for
あの空
that sky.
背伸びして
Standing on tiptoes,
星をつかむ
to grab a star,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate it.
負けないで
Don't lose,
願いさえも
even to the wishes
飲み込む闇
that the darkness swallows.
それでも
Even so,
手探りで
groping blindly,
夢のかけら
fragments of a dream...
集めにいこうよ
let's go collect them.
Ugh... I think after all this singing...
...my power is still not enough to defeat the giant pink monster.
Ohohohoho!
I heard you, young warrior.
I can help you with your worry.
Legendary weapon Nut Blade will lend you its power.
Is this...
...the voice of the Fire Blade Priestess?
Yes, you are right.
I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade,
if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit to fight the Pink Giant Monster.
Huh! Okay!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon... One!
胸に刻めよ 時代のLeader
Carve it into your heart, the Leader of the era.
見た目よりかは かなりClever
Quite clever, more than meets the eye.
乾いた心 すさむよりは
Rather than letting your dry heart grow wild,
時に泣いてみれば
If you try crying sometimes,
見えてくる
You will start to see.
明日駆けるのは
The one running through tomorrow,
紛れもなく新しい自分
Is undoubtedly a new you.
誰かの為でもなく
Not for the sake of anyone else,
ただもっと上を目指せ
Just aim even higher!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I do, Why I do!
No question!
You know, You know!
Why I do, Why I do! Whoa!
銀の槍が 病んだ未来が
The silver spear, the sick future...
導くんだ 僕らを
...will guide us.
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon... One!
Four!
見えているのに
Even though I can see it,
遥かなGoalは
The distant goal is,
見た目よりかは かなりHard
Much harder than it looks.
君が踏み出す 勇気持てば
If you have the courage to step forward,
やがて開く道が
The path will soon open up.
目指すべき場所 選ぶのは
The one choosing where to aim,
紛れもなく新しい自分
Is undoubtedly a new you.
全てを手にした君は
You, who have obtained everything,
どんな山をも越える
Will cross any mountain!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I do, Why I do!
No question!
You know, You know!
Why I do, Why I do! Whoa!
銀の嵐が
The silver storm,
吹き飛ばすんだ
Will blow it all away!
迷いとか恐れを
Hesitation and fear.
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
On my way!
信じるだけ 突き抜けるぐらい
Just believe, enough to break through.
In the case!
気持ちHigh Pace!
Feeling high pace!
狭まる闇 上目指す
Darkness closes in, aim for the top.
諦めず探し続ける
Don't give up, keep searching.
いつまでも変わらぬ夢
A dream that never changes.
明日世界は So Rainy
Tomorrow the world is so rainy.
Dragon Screamer!
昇る龍のようだ
Like a rising dragon!
銀の光が
The silver light,
呼んだ未来が
The future called forth,
導くんだ 僕らを
Will guide us!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon Screamer!
Why I do, Why I do!
叫ぶ龍のようだ
Like a screaming dragon!
銀の嵐が
The silver storm,
吹き飛ばすんだ
Will blow it all away!
迷いとか恐れを
Hesitation and fear.
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No question!
You have proven me your spirit.
I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you.
I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster.
Now I have the Nut Blade,
I shall continue my journey to defeat the Giant Pink Monster.
If my hunch was right...
Oh no!
What happened to you, almighty dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた。
I was defeated by a pink giant beast.
今は力が入らん。
I have no strength right now.
巣も、破壊されてしまった。
Even my nest was destroyed.
Oh no, that is bad!
I can help you recover,
if you can take me straight to the giant monster in exchange.
任せておけ。
Leave it to me.
偶然から始まる
It starts by chance,
必然のワンシーン
an inevitable scene.
遠くに見えたのは
What I saw in the distance was
揺れる赤色
a swaying red color.
不思議な森の奥で
Deep in the mysterious forest,
見つけた黒い影
I found a black shadow.
何かが始まる予感
A premonition that something would begin,
怖くて逃げ出した
I got scared and ran away.
出会いは
Our meeting was...
終わりに
...leading to the end...
続く
...continuing...
シナリオ
...scenario.
だからわざと遠回りをした
So I purposely took the long way around.
会いたいなんて
That I want to meet you,
触れたいなんて
want to touch you,
話したいなんて
want to talk to you...
思わない
I don't think that.
か弱い君と狡い僕が
You, who are frail, and I, who am cunning...
出会うそれが終わりさ
Our meeting is the end.
残酷だって罵ったって
Even if you curse fate as cruel,
運命は変わらない
destiny won't change.
ああどうして、君がどうして
Ah, why is it you? Why is it?
僕が狼と赤ずきんなんだ
That I am the wolf and you are Little Red Riding Hood?
きっと君は今日も
Surely you will today too,
この道を訪れる
visit this path.
そして僕は今日もずっと
And I will today too, all along,
見守るしかできない
only be able to watch over you.
君はあの木の先で
Beyond that tree,
いつも通り隠れてる
you are hiding as usual.
私は気付かぬフリしたまま
I pretended not to notice
通り過ぎた
as I walked past.
視線は
Our gazes...
絡まない
...don't meet.
声は
Our voices...
届かない
...don't reach.
ため息だけが虚しく重なる
Only our sighs overlap in vain.
会えなくたって
Even if we can't meet,
触れなくたって
even if we can't touch,
話せなくたって
even if we can't talk...
いいから
it's okay.
頼りない君とぎこちない僕が
You, who are unreliable, and I, who am awkward...
そこにいるだけでいいんだ
it's enough just to be there.
これが恋だと言わないなら
If you don't call this love,
言葉なんてなくていい
then words aren't needed.
ああ考えたって、考えたって
Ah, even if I think about it, even if I think about it,
エンディングは変わらない
the ending won't change.
会いたかったんだ
I wanted to meet you.
触れたかったんだ
I wanted to touch you.
話したかった
I wanted to talk.
本当は
The truth is...
かわいい君と優しい僕が
You, who are cute, and I, who am kind...
出会い結ばれるエンド
an ending where we meet and are united.
何回だって
Again and again,
again and again,
神様に願ったよ
I prayed to God.
でも悲しいくらい
But it's so sad,
悲しいくらい
it's so sad,
狼と赤ずきんなんだ
that we are the wolf and Little Red Riding Hood.
泣いてる君を慰めたくて
I wanted to comfort you crying.
伸ばした腕が震える
My outstretched arm trembles.
愛しているよ
I love you.
抱きしめたいよ
I want to hold you.
だけどできないんだよ
But I can't do it.
どう足掻いたって
No matter how much I struggle,
どう願ったって
no matter how much I wish,
爪も牙も消えない
my claws and fangs won't disappear.
だからただ待ってるよ
So I'll just wait
君の涙が止むまで
until your tears stop.
あの木の先で
Beyond that tree...
ずっと
...forever.
Ah, here you go!
If you eat this, you can recover super quick.
感謝する。
My thanks.
よし、完全回復だ。
Alright, full recovery.
今すぐ怪獣のもとへ、案内しよう。
I will guide you to the monster right now.
Okay, let's go!
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙
Sweat, blood, and tears...
今全部全部を蹴散らして跳べ
Kick everything, everything aside and jump!
Fly High!!
高く Fly High!!
High, Fly High!!
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest future.
傷だらけの若鳥が空を
A scarred young bird is staring...
睨んでる
...at the sky.
低空飛行する奴らが
Even if those flying at low altitudes...
笑おうと海の果てが見たい
...laugh at me, I want to see the end of the sea.
心を無にして
Emptying my mind,
向かい風に乗り
Riding the headwind,
助走をつけて
I gain momentum.
Hop step jump で
With a hop, step, jump...
跳べ Fly High!! Ah...
Jump, Fly High!! Ah...
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が
these shining wings...
君をどこへだって連れて行く
...will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と本能と
With blue impulses and instinct,
爪牙をむき出しにして
baring fangs and claws.
艱難の旅路も
Even on a difficult journey,
夢叶うまで
until the dream comes true...
何度だって
...as many times as it takes!
跳べ Fly High!!
Jump, Fly High!!
高く Fly High!!
High, Fly High!!
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest future.
ぽつり降り出した雨が
The rain that started falling drop by drop...
翼狂わせる
...throws my wings off balance.
行く手には黒い雲
Dark clouds block the way.
今長い嵐の夜が来る
Now, a long stormy night is coming.
轟く雷鳴と
With roaring thunder...
砕ける波頭を
...and breaking waves...
飾りにして
...as my decorations...
アングリー・ロードは
On this Angry Road...
跳べ Fly High!! Ah...
Jump, Fly High!! Ah...
いつも胸の奥を
The flame that always...
焦がす炎が
...scorches deep in my chest...
道を照らし出す
...illuminates the path,
灯台になる
becoming a lighthouse.
夜明け前の攻防が
The struggle before dawn...
才能の花咲かすから
...will make the flower of talent bloom.
命尽きるまで
Until my life runs out,
限界を超え
exceed the limit...
最高速で跳べ Fly High!!
...and jump at top speed, Fly High!!
跳べ Fly High!! Ah...
Jump, Fly High!! Ah...
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears,
光る翼が
these shining wings...
君をどこへだって連れて行く
...will take you anywhere.
青い衝動と本能と
With blue impulses and instinct,
爪牙をむき出しにして Yeah!
baring fangs and claws. Yeah!
全部全部を蹴散らして
Kick everything, everything aside...
跳べ Fly High!! Ah...
...and Jump, Fly High!! Ah...
いつも胸の奥を
The flame that always...
焦がす炎が
...scorches deep in my chest...
道を照らし出す
...illuminates the path,
灯台になる
becoming a lighthouse.
夜明け前の攻防が
The struggle before dawn...
才能の花咲かすから
...will make the flower of talent bloom.
命尽きるまで
Until my life runs out,
限界を超え
exceed the limit...
最高速で跳べ Fly High!!
...and jump at top speed, Fly High!!
高く Fly High!!
High, Fly High!!
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest future.
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you, would you...
Kecil dahulu
Small in the past
The love will last, it will
Selamanya ku kan peduli
Forever I will care
To me, broken thing have I become
And you see love is pain
Truly I...
I've never had enough
Ordinary days
It seems the clouds over us
In the sky painted
Coloring my paradise
Titik hujan membasahkan segala
Raindrops wet everything
Luka duka emosi manusia
Wounds, grief, human emotions
Tak akan berkabar
Will not bring news
Melenyapkan segalanya
Obliterating everything
Will I love you like you love me too
Utarakanlah lebih dahulu
Express it first
The love will last, it will
Selamanya ku kan ada di sini
Forever I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become
And you see love is fabulous
Truly I...
I will never let me down
Ordinary days
It seems the clouds over us
In the sky painted
Coloring my paradise
Titik hujan menghapuskan segala
Raindrops erasing everything
Luka duka emosi manusia
Wounds, grief, human emotions
Rapuh dan terjatuh
Fragile and fallen
Lelah di dunia
Tired of the world
The hymn of love
Lingers on my ego
Blinding lights that radiates
Evaporates the scent in me
A soundless whisper follow me
Don't you ever let go
Bahagia hanya jadi
Happiness only becomes
Hanya jadi benalu
Only becomes a parasite
To me, obsessive have I become
And you see love is over us
Truly I...
I will never give enough
Ordinary...
I will be the clouds and the color of rainbow
Start to show me my
Paradise
Titik hujan meleburkan segala
Raindrops melting everything
Luka duka emosi manusia
Wounds, grief, human emotions
Rapuh dan berlalu
Fragile and passing
Lelah di dunia
Tired of the world
How I finally get through to meet you
I will kill off your bad mood
Titik hujan membasuh bersih
Raindrops wash clean
Suka dan duka perasaan dan
Joy and grief, feelings and...
Melebur satu warna
Merging into one color
Yang bermakna
That is meaningful
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the nut-nut from misery!
Whoa!
I can't believe that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute!
Aww!
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ひらひら 落ち好き
Fluttering, falling moon.
夜明けが見たいって 叫んだ空
I screamed at the sky that I wanted to see the dawn.
ヒビ割れた雲 影と影の忍び寄る
Cracked clouds, shadows creeping up on shadows.
深く刺さった痛みとそして混じろ
Pain pierced deep, and now mingle.
光る光る照らし出す
Shining, shining, illuminating...
申請の夢
...a dream of application.
叩く 叩く 甘い ヒバリ
Strike, strike, sweet skylark.
神様気取りの真似模たちが
Those imitating gods...
世界を愛して壊しました
...loved the world and broke it.
誰の物 誰の物 我の物
Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine.
邪魔者は排除した
I eliminated the intruders.
感度がなんとか言ってたって
Even if you talk about sensitivity...
エゴに掴まれて拒めないんだ
...seized by ego, you can't refuse.
物足りない 物足りない 死にたくない
Not enough, not enough, I don't want to die.
機械仕掛けの腐った声で
With a rotten, mechanical voice...
大人たちが言う
...the adults speak.
うんざりだよ
I'm fed up.
シンドローム 愛してるわ
Syndrome. I love you.
もうやめてよ！
Stop it already!
心で物を量って切って
Measuring and cutting things with your heart...
売れば幸せですか？
...if you sell them, are you happy?
作られた憧憬 もどかしたい基盤
Fabricated longing, a foundation I want to frustrate.
世界 虚ろの果て
The world, the end of the void.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
感情 科学より不良
Emotions are more defective than science.
天津乙女 歌と舞う
Heavenly maiden, dance with the song.
ヒバリの空
Skylark's sky.
輪廻転生 機械論 進化の論
Reincarnation, mechanism, theory of evolution.
人が人でなくなる
Humans cease to be human.
血に塊をこらえろと
Endure the clots in your blood.
歌だけは未来へ届くよ
Only songs will reach the future.
空から空へと繋げるよ
Connecting sky to sky.
限りなく鳴くヒバリ ヒバリたちは
Endlessly singing skylarks, the skylarks...
残す
...leave behind.
なんてアホウを聞かせてくれたっけ
What kind of foolishness did you tell me?
メリヤスありのこと 愛してる
I love the knitted fabric of reality.
嘘でもいいから一度だけでも
Even if it's a lie, just once...
聞かせてよ
...let me hear it.
どこ寄ってどこで笑ってました？
Where did you stop by and where did you laugh?
今は幸せですか？
Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま 届かない想い
Left behind, feelings that don't reach.
ごめん なんで言えなかったかな
Sorry, I wonder why I couldn't say it.
悲しい思い出は風に隠した
I hid the sad memories in the wind.
歌よ あなたの元へ
Song, go to where you are.
天津乙女 時を舞う
Heavenly maiden, dance through time.
ヒバリの空
Skylark's sky.
独りでも笑って生きるんだ
I'll live smiling, even if I'm alone.
独りでは生きてゆけないんだ
I can't go on living alone.
ずっと拒んだり 愛したり
Always refusing, loving...
裏で壊してそれでも縋って生きるよ
...breaking things behind the scenes, yet still clinging on to live.
心で物を量って切って
Measuring and cutting things with your heart...
売れば幸せですか？
...if you sell them, are you happy?
作られた憧憬 もどかし
Fabricated longing, frustrating...
切ない期待 未来
...painful expectation, future.
行き先の鍵
The key to the destination.
魂を一体どこに隠した？
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
感情 科学より不良
Emotions are more defective than science.
天津乙女 歌と舞う
Heavenly maiden, dance with the song.
夜明けを告げたら
When the dawn is announced...
ヒバリの空
...Skylark's sky.
Everyone! Woo!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance? Did you like it? Did you guys have fun?
And also, for celebrating my victory and my birthday...
...we have special merch!
Yes! So here is the merch!
Woo-hoo! Whoa!
Birthday Set
How cool is it?
And it's not only cool.
This year's merch was designed to be useful too. So let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh! Whoa! It's an awesome A3 Tapestry drawn by netural-sensei.
A3タペストリー
A3 Tapestry
Whoa! The whole illustration just... woah. It looks super awesome.
It looks so cool. You can see that I'm holding my beloved... *clears throat*
Just look at that Warrior Risu with full dark side.
Isn't it awesome? Woo!
Don't miss it. And also don't forget you guys gotta buy it at least five, okay?
And I think let's see what we have next.
タンブラー
Tumbler
Woo! A super cute tumbler!
For everybody, so you guys won't forget to hydrate.
Um, you can use it to drink water and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it every day, okay? And next we have this!
リススマホリング
Squirrel Smartphone Ring
Whoa, a smartphone ring? Ooh!
So you can be um, super comfortable and remember me when you're um, holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand. Very, very convenient.
And I think let's see the full set now! Woo!
Birthday Set
Whoa, there's so much stuff actually.
And also don't forget we have the full set purchase bonus here!
誕生日記念フルセット
Birthday Commemorative Full Set
コルセット購入特典
Full Set Purchase Bonus
So I will explain it a little bit. Uh, for those of you who purchase the full set...
...will also receive a signed foil-stamped postcard.
And for my super Risu-nuts who purchase the Limited Edition Full Set...
...will receive a postcard autographed by none other than me.
Autographed by me! Isn't it awesome? Whoa!
And the preorder window is only a month. So make sure that you don't miss it.
Oh, oh, oh, oh! Also one more thing. Did you guys listen to my new original song?
'Hoshi ga Furu'?
It will be officially released after this stream at midnight JST.
JST, okay? On my YouTube channel.
So go listen to it and *cough* maybe who knows that later we will have MV for it? I don't know!
And last but not least, for all of you who joined my membership...
...you don't want to miss a special additional 3D performance in membership...
...just right after this show has ended.
If you haven't joined my membership yet, do not hesitate because the extra show is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for? Join membership now! Woo!
*Laughs* Oops.
But I think the time is up.
And I have to continue. But yes, I have to continue with the membership show now.
So thank you so much everyone for your support for this whole six years especially.
And thank you for celebrating my birthday together with me.
So! Otsu-Risu!
Sound effects
・有限会社デー・スリー・プロジェクト・
濱子 佑一
Sound effects
Day Three Project Inc.
Yuichi Hamako
Planning
Ayunda Risu
Cinematography
カバー株式会社
Cover Corporation
General Direction
Ayunda Risu
カバー株式会社
General Direction
Ayunda Risu
Cover Corporation
Produced by
Ayunda Risu
Written and Directed by
The Rise of the Nut Warrior